[
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "Unified digital identity systems have many academic benefits, says expert",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "Unified digital identity systems have many academic benefits, says expert is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "General Current Affairs",
      "subject": "General Current Affairs"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "Special package for Amaravati is on wishlist of CII A.P. ahead of Union Budget",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "Special package for Amaravati is on wishlist of CII A.P. ahead of Union Budget is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "Economy",
      "subject": "Economy"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "Can Palaniswami veto AIADMK general council\u2019s decision against Panneerselvam?",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "Can Palaniswami veto AIADMK general council\u2019s decision against Panneerselvam? is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "General Current Affairs",
      "subject": "General Current Affairs"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "HPS parents allege mismanagement, protest arbitrary fee hike and demand govt intervention",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "HPS parents allege mismanagement, protest arbitrary fee hike and demand govt intervention is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "Economy",
      "subject": "Economy"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "HC impleads Govindan as party to pleas challenging Navakerala survey",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "HC impleads Govindan as party to pleas challenging Navakerala survey is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "General Current Affairs",
      "subject": "General Current Affairs"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "YSRCP leader Ambati Rambabu arrested for \u2018creating hurdles\u2019 for police",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "YSRCP leader Ambati Rambabu arrested for \u2018creating hurdles\u2019 for police is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "General Current Affairs",
      "subject": "General Current Affairs"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "Forensic scientists visit drug manufacturing lab in Mysuru",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "Forensic scientists visit drug manufacturing lab in Mysuru is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "Polity",
      "subject": "Polity"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "Private transport federation urges State to move Supreme Court against bike taxi order",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "Private transport federation urges State to move Supreme Court against bike taxi order is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "Polity",
      "subject": "Polity"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "KCR faults wall pasting of letter by phone-tapping case IO, says he\u2019s ready for examination today",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "KCR faults wall pasting of letter by phone-tapping case IO, says he\u2019s ready for examination today is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "General Current Affairs",
      "subject": "General Current Affairs"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "Bishop attends Gunadala Lourdu Matha Mahotsavams",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "Bishop attends Gunadala Lourdu Matha Mahotsavams is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "General Current Affairs",
      "subject": "General Current Affairs"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "India\u2019s media sector undergoing rapid transformation: Union Minister L. Murugan",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "India\u2019s media sector undergoing rapid transformation: Union Minister L. Murugan is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "General Current Affairs",
      "subject": "General Current Affairs"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "BJP demands Supreme Court-monitored SIT probe into Anandapur warehouse fire",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "BJP demands Supreme Court-monitored SIT probe into Anandapur warehouse fire is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "Polity",
      "subject": "Polity"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "Anandapur\u00a0warehouse fire\u00a0puts spotlight\u00a0on illegal construction on East Kolkata Wetlands",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "Anandapur\u00a0warehouse fire\u00a0puts spotlight\u00a0on illegal construction on East Kolkata Wetlands is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "General Current Affairs",
      "subject": "General Current Affairs"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "Tharoor signals active involvement in UDF\u2019s Assembly campaign\u00a0after meeting Kerala Opposition leader",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "Tharoor signals active involvement in UDF\u2019s Assembly campaign\u00a0after meeting Kerala Opposition leader is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "Polity",
      "subject": "Polity"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "Many promotee IAS officers from Karnataka reluctant to attend induction training at Mussoorie",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "Many promotee IAS officers from Karnataka reluctant to attend induction training at Mussoorie is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "General Current Affairs",
      "subject": "General Current Affairs"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "Kerala for All: Final day of conclave to deliberate on shaping the future of Kerala tourism",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "Kerala for All: Final day of conclave to deliberate on shaping the future of Kerala tourism is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "General Current Affairs",
      "subject": "General Current Affairs"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "TDP activists protest Ambati Rambabu\u2019s comments on Naidu in Guntur",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "TDP activists protest Ambati Rambabu\u2019s comments on Naidu in Guntur is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "Polity",
      "subject": "Polity"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "Over 6,000 take part in The Hindu Business Line cerebration quiz, Hyderabad regional round today",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "Over 6,000 take part in The Hindu Business Line cerebration quiz, Hyderabad regional round today is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "General Current Affairs",
      "subject": "General Current Affairs"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "Centre forms expert panel on healthcare for transgender persons",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "Centre forms expert panel on healthcare for transgender persons is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "General Current Affairs",
      "subject": "General Current Affairs"
    }
  },
  {
    "date": "2026-01-31",
    "topic": "El Nino on the horizon during monsoon months",
    "source": "The Hindu",
    "mcq": {
      "question": "El Nino on the horizon during monsoon months is related to which of the following?",
      "options": [
        "Economy",
        "Polity",
        "Science & Tech",
        "Defence"
      ],
      "answer": "General Current Affairs",
      "subject": "General Current Affairs"
    }
  }
]